好了现在是时候了我要卷起老袖子了
All right, so now it's the time,
I'm gonna roll up the old sleeves.
现实地，从比喻上说，不管你想要什么都可以。
Realistically, metaphorically,
proverbially, whatever you want.
我建议，在此部分，我建议关闭您的笔记本电脑。
I recommend, at this portion,
I recommend, close your laptops.
太诱惑人了
It's too tempting to look stuff up.
在一个真正的采访中，你不能去谷歌，你不能把手机拿出来。
In a real interview, you can't go on
Google, you can't pull out your phone.
我推荐一张纸和笔，旧的学校或白板，如果你有的话。
I recommend a piece of paper and a pen,
old school or whiteboard, if you have one.
如果你在教室里和一群人一起工作
If you're watching this at your work
with a bunch of people in a classroom,
白板也很好
a whiteboard is good too.
但实践它喜欢的代码。
But practice what it's like to code.
只是精神上，完全不使用电脑。
Just mentally,
not using a computer at all.
这里没有画家这里没有帮手
There's no linters,
there's no helpers here.
我真的觉得如果你这么做
And I really think if you do these,
你会更了解我们在这里解决的问题
you'll understand much stronger about
the problems we're gonna solve here.
好吧为了这个挑战
All right, so for this challenge,
我希望您创建一个函数来反转字符串。
I want you to create a function
to reverse a string.
我甚至给了你一些，我甚至给你提供了一些样本输出。
I even gave you some, I even helpfully
gave you some sample output here.
我不想说这是一个热身的问题，但这是一个热身的问题。
I don't wanna say it's a warm up question,
but it is kind of warm up question.
如果你有麻烦的话没关系
If you had a little trouble, that's okay.
我们将在没有电脑的情况下使用代码。
We're going to get used to the coding
without our computers for a bit.
我当然了
I of course,
我要用我的电脑，因为如果我把它写出来，你可以读我的书。
I'm gonna use my computer because you
can read my writing if I wrote it out.
我被告知我不允许用白板是因为我的笔迹
And I was told I'm not allowed to use
a whiteboard because my handwriting is
很残暴
atrocious.
所以我要在这里编码但我不打算把它给跑了
So I'm just gonna code it here but
I'm not gonna run it.
对于这一特殊功能，我希望它是正确的。
For this particular function I
want it to be actually correct.
我接下来要问的很多问题
A lot of the questions
I'm gonna ask later,
如果你到球场去我觉得挺好的
if you get in the ball park
I think that's pretty good.
采访者能得到一个好的概念就足以让他们明白
It's enough for the interviewer to get a
good concept of like they understand what
你在说什么
you're talking about.
您可能缺少括号或分号，这不重要。
You might be missing a bracket or
a semicolon, it doesn't matter.
虽然这只
For this one, though,
我想用很多方法来把它弄明白
I would wanna get it pretty accurate
since there's many ways to do it.
我不会说这是错误的
And I won't say there's a wrong way,
但有更有效的方法去做
but there are more efficient
ways to do it than others.
所以我要用一个 Jem 的小费
So for this one,
I'm gonna say use a Jem tip,
这就是我们想要的
which is talk outs what we want.
所以我想要一个功能，我要把它叫做逆向 cuz ，就是他们所称的。
So I want a function, and I'm gonna call
it reverse cuz that's what they called it.
我知道这个功能会带一个绳子
And I know that function's
gonna take a string.
很酷这才是个好开始
Cool, this is a good starting place.
如果你被困住了就跟你说你想要什么
If you ever get stuck,
just talk out what you want.
如果他们想要一个能让它后来被调用的功能
If they want a function that
it's gonna be later invoked,
您知道需要一个返回另一个函数的函数。
you know you want a function
that returns another function.
然后说出去
And by talking that out and
得到这个结构真的能帮你精神上的了解
getting the structure really
helps you mentally picture it.
所以我想反转一个字符串，有几种方法可以做到这一点。
So I want to reverse a string,
there's a few ways to do this.
我要用我能想到的最短的时间来做这个
I'm gonna do this in the shortest
way that I can think of.
因此，我希望返回一个字符串。
So I want to return a string.
但我不会再创造一个新的了
But I'm not going to create a new one yet.
我要做的就是把那串分开
So what I'm gonna do is I'm
gonna split that string.
分割，它执行的是字符串，将其分解为数组。
Split, what that does is it takes
the string, breaks it into an array.
现在我可以用相反的方式
And now I can use reverse.
我知道有些人就像我在一个循环里
I know, some of you are like I
reverse iterated over a loop and
那我就一起回去
then I'm gonna join it back together.
正反转一个字符串。
And that is reversing a string.
再次，您可以使用 for 循环。
Again, you could use a for loop.
您可以进入数组，使用 for 循环，然后向后迭代
You could break into an array, use a for
loop, and iterate over it backwards and
那就回去吧
return that.
这也会起作用，这就是我们在这里所做的。
That would also work,
this is essentially what we're doing here.
这只是用在实用程序中为我们做的。
This is just using those built in
utility methods to do it for us.
好吧没那么糟吧
All right, not too bad, yes?
> > 这样问采访者是个好地方，对吧 ?
&gt;&gt; So this would be a good place to
ask the interviewer a question, right?
我能用倒转吗
May I use reverse?
[ LAUGH] >> 是，是。
[LAUGH]
&gt;&gt; Yeah, yeah.
一般来说这些和大多数访谈都是
Generally for these and
for most interviews,
除非他们明确表示不要做什么
unless they explicitly
say don't do something.
在这两个问题上，我会要求你编码。
And in about two questions there
will be something I ask you to code.
我说，别用这个方法，它会为你做。
And I'll say, don't use this
method cuz it'll do it for you.
但我想看看你是怎么想的
But this is something I
want to see how you think.
一般我觉得你可以用什么工具
Generally I think you're fine
to use whatever tools you can.
再一次，你是白板编码的大部分时间。
Cuz again, you're whiteboard
coding these most of the time.
好吧那就好了
All right, so that was good,
我知道你们中有些人可能有点用纸张上的编码来挣扎
I know some of you probably struggled
a little bit with coding on paper.
这有点奇怪，但这才是真正的访谈。
It's a little weird, but
this is how a real interview would go.
能锻炼肌肉就好了
It's good to get those muscles going.
但一般来说，我常说，如果可能的话，请使用数组。
But in general, I always say,
use an array if possible.
阵列是我最喜欢的数据结构之一。
Array is one of my
favorite data structures.
你可以用数组方法来做任何事情。
You can do pretty much anything
you wanna do with array methods.